Hilpert, Elmer E. Arbitration Papers 5493
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Holliston Mills, Inc. vs. IBT, Local 549, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  9/24/73. Issue: assignment of jobs - overtime
- Hopper Paper Co. vs. UPP, Local 229, 1962 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  6/4/62. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Hotel Association of St. Louis vs. Building Service Employees' Int'l. Union, Local 50, 1956 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  5/22/56. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Hubbell Metals, Inc. vs. IBT, Local 688, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  10/10/73. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Hudson Chemical Co. vs. Building Service Employees' Int'l. Union, Local 50, 1954 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  3/8/54. Issue: vacations - eligibility.
- Hughes Tool Co. vs. USA, Local 1742, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  11/24/69. Issue: overtime - failure to schedule
- Hughes Tool Co. vs. USA, Local 1742, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  5/11/71. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Hughes Tool Co. vs. USA, Local 1742, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  11/23/72. Issue: promotions - seniority
- Hughes Tool Co. vs. USA, Local 1742, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  11/30/72. Issue: discipline - layoff
- Hughes Tool Co. vs. USA, Local 1742, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  9/16/72. Issue: discipline - suspension, discharge
- Hughes Tool Co. vs. USA, Local 1742, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  12/9/72. Issue: discipline - layoff
- Hughes Tool Co. vs. USA, Local 1742, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  11/30/73. Issue: discipline - layoff
- Hughes Tool Co. vs. USA, Local 1742, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  11/3/73. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Hunter Packing Co. vs. MCBW, Local 530, 1951 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  4/19/51. Issue: holiday pay
- Hunter Packing Co. vs. IBEW, Local 309, 1952 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  5/23/52. Issue: call in - rates of pay
- Hussman Refrigerator Co. vs. Stove Mounters' Int'l. Union, Local 110 and others, 1957 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  11/11/57. Issue: rates of pay - reporting pay
- Hussman Refrigerator Co. vs. Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators and Paperhangers of America, Local 980, 1959 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  4/21/59. Issue: vacation pay
- Hussman Refrigerator Co. vs. CJA, St. Louis, 1960 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  8/31/60. Issue: seniority
- Hussman Refrigerator Co. vs. PPF, Local 562., 1961 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  5/16/61. Issue: seniority
- Hussman Refrigerator Co. vs. Stove Mounters Int'l. Union of North America, Local 110, 1960 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  7/14/60. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Illinois Cities Water Co. vs. IBEW, Local 702, 1959 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  4/17/59. Issue: promotion - seniority
- Illinois Power Co. vs. Int'l. Hod Carriers, Building and Common Laborers' Union, Local 397, 1959 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  8/27/59. Issue: discipline - discharge - insubordination
- Illinois Power Co. vs. Int'l. Hod Carriers', Building and Common Laborers' Union, Local 1136, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  4/12/66. Issue: assignment of jobs - outside unit
- Illinois State Bank of East Alton vs. Office Employees Int'l. Union, Local 13, 1957 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  8/21/57. Issue: union security - union shop
- Illinois Terminal Railroad Co. vs. Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen (BRT), Local 481., 1957 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  5/1/57. Issue: termination - union shop - refusal to join union
- Indian Head Co. - Laurens Glass Co. vs. GBBA, 1969 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  5/19/69. No decision
- Indian Head Co. - Laurens Glass Co. vs. GBBA, 1969 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  6/9/69. No decision
- Indian Head Co. - Laurens Glass Co. vs. GBBA, Local 143, 1970 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  3/28/70. Issue: assignment of jobs
- Indian Head, Inc., Obear-Nester Glass Co. vs. GBBA, Local 78., 1971 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  8/29/71. Issue: vacation pay - termination of employment
- Indian Head, Inc., Obear-Nester Glass Co. vs. GBBA, Local 78, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 5-6)
  8/26/71. Issue: severance pay
- Inland Cold Storage Co. vs. IBT, Local 838, 1966 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  8/19/66. No decision
- IBEW, Local 1439 vs. Office Employees' Int'l. Union, Local 13, 1957 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  6/18/57. Issue: contracts -automatic renewal
- International Chemical Corp. vs. ICW, Local 417 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- International Harvester Co. vs. UMW, District 50, Local 14,777, 1962 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  9/28/62. Issue: layoff - recall
- Int'l. Paper Co., Bagpak Division vs. Int'l. Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, Local 473, 1965 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  10/5/65. No decision
- Int'l. Paper Co. vs. Int'l. Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, Local 604., 1966 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  12/12/66. No decision
- Int'l. Paper Co., Southern Kraft Division vs. UPIU, Local 731, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  11/30/72. Issue: assignment of jobs - temporary assignment
- Int'l. Shoe co., Cape Girardeau, Missouri vs. USW, Local 125-A, 1954 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  2/15,16,18/54. Issue: rates of pay.
- Int'l. Shoe Co., Eldon, Missouri vs. USW, Local 219, 1953 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  8/9/53. Issue: rates of pay
- Int'l. Shoe Co., Eldon, Missouri vs. USW, Local 219, 1954 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  6/15/54. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Int'l Shoe Co., Rubber Plant, Hannibal, Missouri vs. URW, Local 198, 1966 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  5/4/66. Issue: insurance benefits
- Int'l. Shoe Co., Hannibal, Missouri vs. URW, Local 198, 1966 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  5/20/66. No decision
- Int'l. Shoe Co., Sikeston, Missouri vs. USW, Local 123-A, 1953 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  8/22/53. Issue: rates of pay
- Interstate Paper Corp. vs. UPIU, Local 354, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  3/5/73. Issue: discipline - layoff
- Iowa Power and Light Co. vs. IBEW, Local 499, 1958 (Box 48, Folder 21-22)
  8/27/58. Issue: management rights - change of work schedule
- Iowa Power and Light Co. vs. IBEW, Local 499, 1958 (Box 48, Folder 23)
  9/19/58. Issue: layoff - seniority
- Jakes-Evans Manufacturing Co. vs. Stove Mounters Int'l. Union, Local 100, 1957 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  12/15/57. Issue: illness - vacation pay
- Jackson Garment Co. vs. ILGWU, 1956 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  4/2/56. Settled
- Jefferson Chemical Co. vs. OCAW, Local 4-228, 1958 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  3/14/58. Issue: assignment of jobs - shift preference
- Jefferson Chemical Co. vs. OCAW, Local 4-228, 1964 (Box 49, Folder 4-5)
  10/31/64. Issue: absences - excessive
- Jefferson City Cabinet Co. vs. IUE, Local 748., 1968 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  10/18/68. Issue: assignment of jobs - shift scheduling
- Jensen-Salsbery Labs vs. United Packinghouse and Allied Workers, Local 150, 1966 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  10/26/66. Issue: posting - refusal to post
- John Hancock Mutual Life Insurance Co. vs. Insurance Workers Int'l. Union (IWIU), 1963 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  10/30/63. Issue: disability - reinstatement
- Jonathan Stores, Inc. vs. MCBW, Local 88, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  4/7/71. Issue: termination of employment - police record
- Johns-Manville Corp. vs. UPP, Local 805, 1962 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  7/5/62. Issue: classification of jobs - combination of classifications
- Jones and Laughlin Stell Corp. vs. USA, Local 3449., 1966 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  6/14/66. Issue: discipline - reprimand - absence
- Joy Manufacturing Co. vs. UE, Local 810, 1954 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  12/10/54. Issue: classification of jobs
- KXOK Broadcasting, Inc. vs. American Federation of Television and Radio Artists (AFTRA), St. Louis Local, 1959 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  2/25/59. Issue: rates of pay
- Kaiser Aluminum and Chemical Corp., Gramercy, Louisiana vs. USA, Local 5702, 1965 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  1/28/65. Issue: assignment of jobs - seniority
- Kaiser Aluminum and Chemical Corp., Newark, Ohio vs. USA, Local 314, 1958 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  10/17/58. Issue: discipline - suspension - warning
- Kansas City Board of Utilities vs. IBEW, Local 53, 1950 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  11/11/50. Issue: rates of pay
- Kansas City Power and Light Co. vs. IBEW, Local 1613., 1965 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  2/10/65. Issue: holidays and holiday pay.
- Katz Drug Co. vs. Retail Store Employees Union, Local 782, 1965 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  9/6/65. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Kawneer Co., Inc. vs. USA, Local 6139, 1965 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  10/11/65. No decision
- Kearney, James R., Corp. vs. Warehouse and Distribution Workers' Union, Local 688, 1963 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  12/23/63. Issue: sick leave and sick pay
- Kearney National, Inc. - Kearney Co. vs. Warehouse and Distribution Workers' Union, Local 688, 1968 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  2/17/68. Issue: arbitrability - timeliness; sick leave and sick pay
- Kearney National, Inc. - Kearney Co. vs. Warehouse and Distribution Workers' Union, Local 688, 1968 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  10/1/68. No decision
- Kearney and Trecker Corp. vs. IAM, Lodge 76., 1969 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  1/6/69. Issue: overtime
- Keasbey and Mattison Co. vs. CLGW, Local 36, 1961 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  5/9/61. Issue: overtime - assignment of jobs.
- Kellogg Co. vs. AFGM, Local 252, 1967 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  5/23/67. Issue: discipline - discharge.
- Kendall Co. vs. TWUA., 1965 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  6/18/65. Issue: discipline - discharge.
- Keokuk Steel Castings Co. vs. USA, 1947 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  2/26/47. No decision
- Kerr Manufacturing Corp. vs. GBBA, Local 57., 1969 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  7/28/69. Issue: supervisors - inclusion in bargaining unit
- Kerr Glass Manufacturing Corp. vs. URW, Local 285, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  7/31/70. Issue: assignment of jobs - supervisors.
- Kerr Glass Manufacturing Corp. vs. URW, Local 285, 1971 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  4/12/71. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Key Co. vs. IBEW, Local 309, 1952 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  9/23/52. Issue: holidays and holiday pay
- Keystone Steel and Wire Co. vs. Independent Steel Workers' Alliance., 1961 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  8/20/61. Issue: management rights - crew size
- Keystone Steel and Wire Co. vs. Independent Steel Workers' Alliance., 1967 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  5/23/67. Issue: rates of pay
- Kieffer Paper Mills vs. UPP, Local 837, 1969 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  11/9/69. Issue: classification of jobs - job description
- Kimberly-Clark Corp. vs. UPP, Local 566, 1964 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  10/28/64. Issue: discipline - discharge - theft
- King Milling Co. vs. AFGM, Local 217, 1962 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  1/4/62. Issue: vacation pay
- Koch, George, and Sons, Inc. vs. IBT, Local 215, 1971 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  11/20/71. Issue: contracting out.
- Koehring Co. vs. AIW, Local 919., 1974 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  10/8/74. Issue: discharge - wildcat strike.
- Koenig Iron Works vs. USA, Local 6831, 1969 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  8/8/69. Issue: discipline - discharge - absenteeism
- Krause Milling Co. vs. AFGM, Local 8, 1969 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  11/1/69. No award
- Kresge, S. S., Co. vs. RCIA, Local 676, 1973 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  12/10/73. No award
- Krey Packing Co. vs. MCBW, Local 545, 1963 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  9/15/63. Issue: discharge - absences and tardiness
- Krey Packing Co. vs. MCBW, Local 545, 1965 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  5/16/65. Issue: discharge - work breaks
- Krey Packing Co. vs. MCBW, Local 545, 1972 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  3/3/72. Issue: discharge -dishonesty
- Kroger Co., Cincinnati, Ohio, 1959-1970 (Box 52, Folder 12-16)
  No awards
- Kroger Co., Columbus vs. RCIA, Locals 1059, 359, 977, 388, 1534, 188, 1190, 31, 1588 and 1593, 1960 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  5/26/60. Issue: classification of jobs - new agreement - retroactive pay
- Kroger Co., Columbus vs. American Bakery and Confectionery Workers' Int'l. Union, Local 57, 1971 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  2/8/71. Issue: seniority
- Kroger Co., Hazelwood vs. MCBW, Local 88., 1964 (Box 52, Folder 19)
  11/19/64. Issue: discipline - suspension
- Kroger Co., Houston vs. IBT, Local 968, 1969 (Box 52, Folder 20)
  5/26/69. Issue: assignment of jobs - outside unit
- Kroger Co., Kansas City, Missouri vs. MCBW, Local 576, 1965 (Box 52, Folder 21)
  9/27/65. Issue: vacation pay
- Kroger Co., Kansas City, Missouri vs. MCBW, Local 576, 1965 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  11/18/65. Issue: discipline - layoff.
- Kroger Co., Kroger Family Center, Cape Girardeau, Missouri vs. RCIA, Local 986, 1971 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  9/5/71. Issue: rates of pay - retroactive increases
- Kroger Co., Louisville, Kentucky vs. Bakery and Confectionery Workers' Int'l. Union, Local 384, 1958 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  2/17/58. Issue: discipline -discharge
- Kroger Co., Louisville, Kentucky vs. General Drivers, Warehousemen and Helpers, Local 89, 1970 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  3/10/70. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Kroger Co., Louisville, Kentucky vs. General Drivers, Warehousemen and Helpers, Local 89, 1970 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  8/16/70. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Kroger Co., Memphis, Tennessee vs. General Drivers, Salesmen and Warehousemen's Local 984, 1958 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  2/5/58. Issue: schedules of work - overtime
- Kroger Co., Memphis, Tennessee vs. Bakery and Confectionery Workers' Int'l. Union, Local 149, 1974 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  9/19/74. No decision
- Kroger Co., Nashville, Tennessee vs. IBT, Local 327, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  11/28/60. Issue: overtime - remedy for improper assignment
- Kroger Co., Nashville, Tennessee vs. IBT, Local 327, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  11/30/60. Issue: sick leave and sick pay.
- Kroger Co., Owensboro, Kentucky vs. MCBW, Local 227, 1965 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  11/29/65. Issue: assignment of jobs - seniority
- Kroger Co., Peoria, Illinois vs. IBT, Local 627, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  10/12/72. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Kroger Co., St. Louis, Missouri vs. Bakery and Confectionery Workers' Int'l. Union of America, Local 4, 1954 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  5/27/54. Issue: working conditions - crew size.
- Kroger Col, St. Louis, Missouri vs. MCBW, Local 88, 1962 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  9/24/62. Issue: demotions - voluntary demotion
- Kroger Co., St. Louis, Missouri vs. Bakers Union No. 4., 1963 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  10/31/63. Issue: rates of pay
- Kroger Co., St. Louis, Missouri vs. Miscellaneous Drivers and Helpers, Local 610, 1967 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  10/18/67. Issue: rates of pay - overtime
- Kroger Co., St. Louis, Missouri vs. MCBW, Local 88, 1968 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  8/16/68. Issue: arbitrability; discipline - discharge
- Kroger Co., St. Louis, Missouri vs. MCBW, Local 88, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  6/9/72. Issue: vacations - eligibility
- Kroger Co., St. Louis, Missouri vs. Retail Clerks Int'l. Union (RCIU), Local 219, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  4/12/72. Issue: vacations - eligibility
- Kroger Co., St. Louis, Missouri vs. Firemen, Oilers, Maintenance Men and Associated Industries, Local 367, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  6/30/72. Issue: vacations - termination of employment
- Kroger Co., St. Louis, Missouri vs. RCIU, Local 896, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  9/10/73. Issue: holidays and holiday pay.
- LTV Ling Altec, Inc. - University Sound Division vs. IAM, Local 850, 1969 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  1/25/69. Issue: discipline - discharge.
- Laclede Gas Co. vs. OCAW, Local 8-6, 1960 (Box 54, Folder 13-14)
  4/2/60. Issue: working conditions
- Laclede Gas Co. vs. OCAW, Local 8-6, 1960 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  4/30/60. Issue: rates of pay - time not worked.
- Laclede Gas Co. vs. OCAW, Local 8-6, 1960 (Box 55, Folder 1)
- Laclede Gas Co. vs. OCAW, Local 8-6, 1960 (Box 55, Folder 2-3)
  3/5/60. Issue: rates of pay - training programs
- Laclede Gas Co. vs. OCAW, Local 8-6, 1960 (Box 55, Folder 4-5)
  7/22/60. Issue: rates of pay - time not worked.
- Laclede Gas Co. vs. OCAW, Local 8-6, 1960 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  7/24/60. Issue: assignment of overtime
- Laclede Gas Co. vs. OCAW, Local 8-6, 1960 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  7/27/60. Issue: assignment of overtime
- Laclede Gas Co. vs. OCAW, Local 8-6, 1961 (Box 55, Folder 8-9)
  3/11/61. Issue: assignment of jobs - classification of jobs - outside classification
- Laclede Gas Co. vs. OCAW, Local 8-6, 1961 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  3/11/61. Issue: shift scheduling - vacancies.
- Laclede Gas Co. vs. OCAW, Local 8-6, 1961 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  3/11/61. Issue: rates of pay - premium pay - computation of
- Laclede Gas Co. vs. OCAW, Local 5-6, 1964 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  12/12/64. Issue; discipline - discharge - insubordination
- Laclede Steel Co. vs. USA, Local 3643, 1952 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  7/3/52. Issue: discipline - discharge - fights
- Laclede Steel Co. vs. USA, Local 3643, 1955 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  8/22/55. Issue: discipline - discharge - drinking on the job
- Laclede Steel Co. vs. USA, Local 3643, 1958 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  7/3/58. Issue: seniority -bumping
- Laclede Steel Co. vs. USA, Local 3643, 1963 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  12/8/63. Issue: discipline - discharge - misconduct
- Laclede Steel Co. vs. USA, Local 1785, 1956 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  1/25/56. Issue: classification of jobs
- Laclede Steel Co. vs. USA, Local 1785, 1968 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  1/27/68. Issue: discipline - discharge - leaving plant early
- Laclede Steel Co. vs. USA, Local 1785, 1969 (Box 56, Folder 9-11)
  4/20/69. Issue: Discipline - discharge - absences
- Landis Machine Co. vs. USA, Local 3735, 1947 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  11/10/47. Issue: vacation pay
- Landis Machine Co. vs. USA, Local 3735, 1950 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  1/21/50. Issue: seniority - shutdowns
- Landis Machine Co. vs. USA, Local 3735, 1950 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  1/6/50. Issue: seniority - shutdowns
- Landis Machine Co. vs. USA, Local 3735, 1954 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  6/24/54. Issue: rates of pay
- Lefton, B., and Sons Iron and Metal Co. vs. Int'l. Longshoremen's Association (ILA), Local 1765., 1954 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  4/23/54. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Lehigh Portland Cement Co. vs. CLGW, Local 106, 1963 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  1/2/63. Issue: assignment of jobs - seniority.
- Lewin Metals Corp. vs. USA, Local 4294, 1954 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  1/7/54. No decision
- Lewin Metals Corp. vs. USA, Local 4294, 1954 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  1/27/54. Issue: reinstatement
- Lewin Metals Corp. vs. USA, Local 4294, 1954 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  3/6/54. Issue: lunch periods - overtime
- Lewin Metals Corp. vs. USA, Local 4294, 1954 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  5/27/54. Issue: rates of pay - holiday pay.
- Lewin Metals Corp. vs. USA, Local 4294, 1955 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  1/25/55. Issue: overtime; assignment of jobs.
- Lewin Metals Corp. vs. USA, Local 4294, 1956 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  3/18/56. Issue: assignment of jobs - classification
- Lewin Metals Corp. vs. USA, Local 4294, 1956 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  3/6/56. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Lewin Metals Corp. vs. USA, Local 4294, 1957 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  5/23/57. Issue: assignment of jobs - overtime.
- Lianco Container Corp. vs. USA, Local 7328., 1970 (Box 57, Folder 15)
  10/23/70. Issue: assignment of jobs - overtime.
- Lianco Container Corp. vs. USA, Local 7328., 1971 (Box 57, Folder 16)
  4/30/71. Issue: assignment of jobs - shift preference
- Lincoln Engineering Co. vs. UAW, Local 691, 1953 (Box 57, Folder 17)
  2/26/53. Issue: classification of jobs
- Lindell Motor Co. vs. Automobile Transport Chauffeurs, Demonstrators and Helpers, IBT, Local 604, 1953 (Box 57, Folder 18)
  4/1/53. Issue: discipline - negligence and carelessness
- Link-Belt Co. vs. USA, Local 1150, 1965 (Box 57, Folder 19)
  11/29/65. Issue: overtime
- Link-Belt Co. vs. USA, Local 1150, 1967 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  2/4/67. Issue: bumping
- Lipsett Steel Products, Inc. vs. USA, Local 5451, 1962 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  11/14/62. Issue: vacation pay
- Lipsett Steel Products, Inc. vs. USA, Local 5574., 1958 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  3/22/58. Issue: discipline - discharge - insubordination
- Lipsett Steel Products, Inc. vs. USA, Local 5574., 1963 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  8/6/63. Issue: discipline - discharge - absenteeism
- Lipton, Thomas J., Inc. vs. IBT, Local 838, 1972 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  1/15/72. Issue: rates of pay - vacation pay
- Liquid Carbonic Corp. vs. IBT, Local 610, 1969 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  6/15/69. Issue: arbitrability - timeliness; discipline - carelessness
- Lockheed Aircraft Corp. vs. IAM, Local 709, 1962 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  5/10/62. Issue: discipline - layoff - insubordination
- Lockheed Aircraft Corp. vs. IAM, Local 33, 1961 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  11/4/61. Issue: discharge - insubordination
- Logan-Long Co. vs. UPP, Local 202, 1967 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  9/14/67. Issue: absences -unauthorized
- Lohr Distributing Co. vs. IBT, Local 133, 1967 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  9/14/67. Issue: discharge - work breaks
- Lohr Distributing Co. vs. IBT, Local 133, 1971 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  12/20/71. Issue: reinstatement - back pay awards
- Lone Star Brewing Co. vs. United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink and Distillery Workers, Local 110, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  11/27/68. Issue: seniority.
- Lone Star Cement Corp. vs. United Stone and Allied Products Workers of America, Local 143, 1964 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  7/14/64. Issue: shift scheduling - cancellation of shift
- Lone Star Cement Corp. vs. United Stone and Allied Products Workers of America, Local 173, 1971 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  6/22/71. No award
- Lone Star Steel Corp. vs. USA, Local 4134, 1955 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  3/8/55. Issue: assignment of jobs
- Louisville Water Co. vs. American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), Local 1683, 1971 (Box 58, Folder 16)
  8/20/71. No award.
- Ludlow-Saylor Wire Cloth Co. vs. USA, Local 1994, 1960 (Box 58, Folder 17)
  12/20/60. Issue: layoff - seniority
- MPI Industries, Inc. vs. CJA, 1969 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  12/16/69. Issue: rates of pay - reporting pay.
- MSL Industries, Inc., Miami Industries Division vs. USA, Local 6328, 1969 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  12/24/69. Issue: promotions - return to former job
- Magnavox Co. vs. IAM Local 431, 1963 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  6/19/63. Issue: layoff - seniority
- Magnavox Co. vs. IAM Local 431, 1969 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  6/23/69. Issue: overtime - assignment of jobs.
- Magnavox Co. of Tennessee vs. IUE, Local 748, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  10/20/68. Issue: layoff - temporary
- Magnavox Furniture Co., Johnson City, Tennessee vs. IWA, Local 5-313, 1967 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  7/10/67. Issue: layoff - temporary.
- Mallinckrodt Chemical Works, Uranium Division, St. Louis, Missouri vs. Independent Union of Chemical Plant Workers, 1956 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  11/9/56. Issue: overtime.
- Mallinckrodt Chemical Works, Uranium Division, St. Louis, Missouri vs. Independent Union of Chemical Plant Workers, 1957 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  1/16/57. Issue: overtime
- Mallinckrodt Chemical Works, Uranium Division, St. Louis, Missouri vs. Independent Union of Chemical Plant Workers, 1958 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  3/16/58. Issue: overtime
- Mallinckrodt Chemical Works, Uranium Division, St. Louis, Missouri vs. Independent Union of Chemical Plant Workers, 1959 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  5/15/59. Issue: overtime
- Mallinckrodt Chemical Works, Uranium Division, St. Louis, Missouri vs. Independent Union of Chemical Plant Workers, 1959 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  10/22/59. Issue: assignment of jobs - past practice
- Mallinckrodt Chemical Works, St. Louis, Missouri vs. Independent Union of Atomic Workers, 1960 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  6/12/60. Issue: overtime
- Mallinckrodt Chemical Works, St. Louis, Missouri vs. Independent Union of Atomic Workers, 1960 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  6/30/60. Issue: overtime
- Mallinckrodt Chemical Works, St. Louis, Missouri vs. Independent Union of Atomic Workers, 1960 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  9/12/60. Issue: overtime
- Mallinckrodt Chemical Works, St. Louis, Missouri vs. Independent Union of Chemical Plant Workers, 1960 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  10/26/60. Issue: overtime - seniority.
- Mallinckrodt Chemical Works, Weldon Springs, Missouri vs. Independent Union of Atomic Workers, 1961 (Box 59, Folder 16)
  2/25/61. Issue: discipline - accident proneness.
- Mallinckrodt Chemical Works, St. Louis, Missouri vs. Independent Union of Chemical Plant Workers., 1961 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  6/15/61. Issue: assignment of jobs - assignment to work outside classification.
- Mallinckrodt Chemical Works, St. Louis, Missouri vs. Independent Union of Chemical Plant Workers., 1961 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  10/3/61. Issue: overtime
- Mallinckrodt Chemical Works, St. Louis, Missouri vs. Independent Union of Chemical Plant Workers., 1961 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  12/15/61. Issue: overtime